Guide to the Collège de la Sainte Famille Collection AD.MC.028
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Men and teachers at award ceremony. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1999 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1164)
  Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Awards; Ceremonies; Photographic Prints; Medals/Insignia; Priests/Clergymen; Color Photography; Men; Teachers; Italian Writing; Group Portraits; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair; Events/Occasions; Carpets/Rugs; Ceremonies
- Men eating at school event. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1999 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1168)
  Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Drinks/Beverages; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Color Photography; Men; Food; Priests/Clergymen; Italian Writing; Group Portraits; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair; Events/Occasions; Furnishings
- School staff with clergymen. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1999 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1169)
  Religious Crosses; Food; Drinks/Beverages; Arabic Writing; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Men; Helwan, Egypt; Religious Crosses; Priests/Clergymen; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Furnishings; Teachers; Color Photography
- School staff with clergymen. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1999 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1170)
  Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Religious Crosses; Priests/Clergymen; Men; Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Photographic Prints; Facial Hair
- Award ceremony. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1173)
  Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Awards; Photographic Prints; Priests/Clergymen; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits; Schools/Education
- A group singing, the United Arab Republic flag hangs in the background. 8.9 x 14 cm, Crca 1958–1972 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1175)
  Men; Photographic Prints; Women; Helwan, Egypt; Flags; Choirs; Gelatin Silver Prints; Singing/Singers; Microphones; Musical Instruments; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Nuns; Group Portraits; Performing Arts; Pianos
- A girl performing on stage in a school event. 8.9 x 14 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1177)
  Nuns; Photographic Prints; Girls; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Audiences/Spectators; Children; Schools/Education; Priests/Clergymen; Men; Performance Plays; Children; Group Portraits; Women; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Teachers
- School event. 8.9 x 14 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1178)
  Schools/Education; Boys; Nuns; Girls; Men; Women; Helwan, Egypt; Costumes; Photographic Prints; Audiences/Spectators; Priests/Clergymen; Gelatin Silver Prints; Children; Group Portraits
- A young woman giving a speech at a school event. 8.9 x 14 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1180)
  Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Schools/Education; Microphones; Audiences/Spectators; Men; Students; Gelatin Silver Prints; Speeches; Priests/Clergymen; Photographic Prints; Girls; Women; Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits; Children; Teachers; Performing Arts; Events/Occasions
- Kindergarten class photo. 10.1 x 15.3 cm, Circa 1978-1988 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1181)
  Priests/Clergymen; Bow Ties; Kindergartens/Nurseries; Color Photography; Italian Writing; Men; Arabic Writing; Teachers; Schools/Education; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Women; Children; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Facial Hair
- Kindergarten class photo. 10.1 x 15.3 cm, Circa 1978-1988 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1182)
  Men; Teachers; Women; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Boys; Italian Writing; Children; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Priests/Clergymen; Color Photography; Arabic Writing; Kindergartens/Nurseries; Facial Hair
- Kindergarten class photo. 10.1 x 15.3 cm, Circa 1978-1988 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1183)
  Bow Ties; Arabic Writing; Women; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Men; Kindergartens/Nurseries; Schools/Education; Boys; Children; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Italian Writing; Teachers; Priests/Clergymen; Color Photography; Facial Hair
- First grade class photo. 10.1 x 15.3 cm, Circa 1978-1988 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1184)
  Schools/Education; Teachers; Boys; Children; Helwan, Egypt; Priests/Clergymen; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Bow Ties; Color Photography; Head Covers/Veils; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Men; Women; Facial Hair
- Third grade class photo. 10.1 x 15.3 cm, Circa 1978-1988 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1185)
  Students; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Teachers; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Color Photography; Women; Men; Head Covers/Veils; Children; Photographic Prints; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Facial Hair
- Third grade class photo. 10.1 x 15.3 cm, Circa 1978-1988 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1186)
  Head Covers/Veils; Color Photography; Group Portraits; Priests/Clergymen; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Women; Teachers; Students; Schools/Education; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair; Children; Boys
- School staff with clergymen. 10.1 x 15.3 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1187)
  Women; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Head Covers/Veils; Group Portraits; Men; Priests/Clergymen; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- Capritage swimming pool. 8.9 x 12.7 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1188)
  Color Photography; Italian Writing; Outdoors; Swimming Pools; Palm Trees; Furnishings; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Architecture; Buildings
- Group portrait of boys in bathing suits. 13.9 x 12.7 cm, 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1189)
  Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Children; Italian Writing; Group Portraits; Boys; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Swimming
- Tug of war at a school event. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, Circa 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1190)
  Men; Students; Schools/Education; Children; Boys; Gelatin Silver Prints; Flags; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Sports; Women; Group Portraits; Events/Occasions; Audiences/Spectators
- Tug of war at a school event. 8.3 x 12.4 cm, Circa 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1191)
  Students; Uniforms; Photographic Prints; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Sports; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Schools/Education; Children; Group Portraits; Events/Occasions; Women
- Boys saluting on top of a human pyramid in a school event. 8.4 x 12.9 cm, 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1192)
  Uniforms; Schools/Education; Boys; Students; Children; Men; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Sports; Group Portraits; Events/Occasions
- Sack race in a school event. 8.9 x 13.8 cm, Circa 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1193)
  Fez/Tarboush; Students; Flags; Schools/Education; Boys; Hats; Sports; Women; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Children; Men; Events/Occasions; Group Portraits; Men
- Boys saluting at a school event. 8.6 x 13.6 cm, Circa 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1194)
  Students; Boys; Photographic Prints; Children; Flags; Fez/Tarboush; Helwan, Egypt; Sports; Schools/Education; Men; Hats; Women; Group Portraits; Events/Occasions; Gelatin Silver Prints
- School event. 6 x 8.7 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1195)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Children; Schools/Education; Audiences/Spectators; Boys; Students; Men; Women; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Flags; Group Portraits; Events/Occasions; Boys; Crowds; Girls
- School event. 6 x 8.7 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1196)
  Schools/Education; Nuns; Boys; Audiences/Spectators; Women; Students; Children; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Priests/Clergymen; Teachers; Events/Occasions; Girls; Women
- Students doing exercises. 8.9 x 13.2 cm, 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1198)
  Teachers; Men; Schools/Education; Students; Photographic Prints; Sports; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Children; Group Portraits; Boys
- Students posing in front of Helwan Observatory. 14.2 x 8.3 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1199)
  Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Children; Students; Boys; Buildings; Photographic Prints; Observatories; Helwan, Egypt; Architecture; Schools/Education
- Priests and a student feeding a giraffe in Giza zoo. 9.6 x 7.5 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1200)
  Priests/Clergymen; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Giza, Egypt; Animals; Boys; Hats; Zoos; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Men; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Boys at the sea front in Suez. 8.9 x 13.6 cm, 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1201)
  Swimming; Boys; Group Portraits; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Suez, Egypt; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Children; Beaches; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Group portrait on a wooden boat. 9.1 x 13.4 cm, 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1202)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Palm Trees; Nile River; Outdoors; Men; Boats/Ships; Swimming; Boys; Photographic Prints; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Helwan, Egypt; Children; Water; Transportation; Facial Hair; Group Portraits
- Group portrait at the beach. 8.9 x 13.6 cm, 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1203)
  Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Umbrellas/Parasols; Swimming; Seas; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Boys; Children; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Beaches; Group Portraits; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Clocks/Watches; Water
- Two boys at the beach. 8.8 x 13.8 cm, 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1204)
  Seas; Egypt; Beaches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Swimming; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Photographic Prints; Boys; Children; Group Portraits; Water
- Two boys playing checkers/draughts. 8.8 x 14.3 cm, 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1205)
  Boys; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Egypt; Toys; Children; Animals; Dogs; Group Portraits
- Boys writing at a table. 9.1 x 14 cm, 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1206)
  Men; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Suez, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Children; Teachers; Priests/Clergymen; Pens/Inkwells; Schools/Education; Group Portraits; Facial Hair
- A castle style building with turrets. 8.4 x 13.5 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1208)
  Photographic Prints; Architecture; Suez, Egypt; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Palm Trees
- Men and boys in front of building. 8.9 x 13.7 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1209)
  Architecture; Suez, Egypt; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Italian Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Doors/Entrances; Photographic Prints; Palm Trees; Men; Buildings; Boys; Group Portraits; Hats
- Students at the Japanese Garden. 8.8 x 13.8 cm, Circa 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1210)
  Boys; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Water; Gardens; Group Portraits; Students; Lakes; Children; Parks; Outdoors; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Schools/Education; Teachers
- Students at the Japanese Garden. 5.9 x 9.1 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1211)
  Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits; Outdoors; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Gardens; Students; Boys; Parks; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Schools/Education
- Japanese Garden in Helwan. 5.8 x 8.7 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1212)
  Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Italian Writing; Statues/Sculptures; Parks; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Water; Gardens; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Outdoors; Schools/Education
- Group portrait on a wooden sculpture. 5.5 x 8.5 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1213)
  Helwan, Egypt; Outdoors; Boys; Students; Group Portraits; Children; Parks; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Statues/Sculptures; Schools/Education
- Group portrait in the Japanese Gardens. 5.7 x 8.5 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1214)
  Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Parks; Children; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Men; Teachers; Outdoors; Boys; Students; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Gardens
- Students at the Japanese Garden. 7.2 x 12.4 cm, 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1215)
  Water; Photographic Prints; Gardens; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits; Outdoors; Boys; Men; Italian Writing; Students; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Children; Schools/Education
- Group portrait. 8.8 x 14 cm, 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1216)
  Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Boys; Children; Priests/Clergymen; Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Palm Trees; Helwan, Egypt; Students; Men; Teachers; Schools/Education; Facial Hair
- Students at Japanese Garden. 7.5 x 10.4 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1217)
  Helwan, Egypt; Water; Children; Photographic Prints; Statues/Sculptures; Outdoors; Boys; Group Portraits; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Students; Gardens; Water; Schools/Education; Teachers; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Students and teachers holding a lamb. 8.9 x 13.7 cm, Circa 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1218)
  Students; Teachers; Boys; Outdoors; Men; Children; Animals; Gelatin Silver Prints; Sheep; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Priests/Clergymen; Gardens; Schools/Education; Group Portraits
- Students in front of the pyramids. 8.8 x 13.9 cm, Circa 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1219)
  Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Hats; Boys; Students; Gelatin Silver Prints; Giza, Egypt; Children; Italian Writing; Pyramids; Group Portraits
- Group portrait. 8.9 x 14.2 cm, Circa 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1220)
  Palm Trees; Outdoors; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Teachers; Men; Uniforms; Students; Group Portraits; Boys; Gelatin Silver Prints; Priests/Clergymen; Children; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Schools/Education; Facial Hair
- Students and man in front of Ford bus. 8.7 x 13.6 cm, Circa 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1221)
  Men; Buses; Students; Boys; Group Portraits; Hats; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Transportation; Children; Teachers; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Group portrait. 8.8 x 13.9 cm, 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1222)
  Students; Men; Boys; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Uniforms; Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints
- School photo. 8.8 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1223)
  Boys; Students; Group Portraits; Men; Uniforms; Photographic Prints; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Group portrait. 8.8 x 13.9 cm, 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1224)
  Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Priests/Clergymen; Group Portraits; Men; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Facial Hair; Children; Priests/Clergymen; Gelatin Silver Prints
- School photo. 8.8 x 13.9 cm, 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1225)
  Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Uniforms; Students; Schools/Education; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Boys; Facial Hair; Gelatin Silver Prints; Children
- School photo. 8.8 x 13.9 cm, 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1226)
  Boys; Men; Uniforms; Schools/Education; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Facial Hair; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Group portrait. 8.7 x 13.8 cm, 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1227)
  Group Portraits; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Men; Students; Boys; Painted Backdrops; Children; Studio Photography; Teachers; Facial Hair; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Group portrait. 8.8 x 13.8 cm, 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1228)
  Uniforms; Students; Group Portraits; Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Teachers; Priests/Clergymen; Studio Photography; Facial Hair; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints
- School photo. 9 x 14.1 cm, 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1229)
  Schools/Education; Students; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Uniforms; Teachers; Men; Boys; Group Portraits; Children; Priests/Clergymen; Facial Hair; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Group portrait. 9.1 x 14.1 cm, 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1230)
  Students; Boys; Group Portraits; Men; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Children; Group Portraits; Priests/Clergymen; Teachers; Schools/Education; Studio Photography; Facial Hair; Gelatin Silver Prints
- School photo. 8.8 x 13.5 cm, 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1231)
  Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Group Portraits; Boys; Women; Photographic Prints; Men; Facial Hair; Children; Priests/Clergymen; Gelatin Silver Prints
- School photo. 8.8 x 13.8 cm, 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1232)
  Group Portraits; Men; Uniforms; Uniforms; Photographic Prints; Students; Helwan, Egypt; Priests/Clergymen; Boys; Children; Teachers; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Schools/Education; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Group portrait. 9 x 12 cm, 1936 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1233)
  Regional/National Dress; Men; Boys; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Facial Hair; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints
- School photo. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1234)
  Boys; Group Portraits; Students; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Men; Uniforms; Children; Teachers; Priests/Clergymen; Schools/Education; Studio Photography; Facial Hair; Gelatin Silver Prints
- View of students playing football in school from above. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1978 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1235)
  Boys; Sports; Students; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Football; Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits; Children; Football; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Students in school. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1978 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1236)
  Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Boys; Students; Children; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Students in school. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1237)
  Boys; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Students; Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Students in school. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1978 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1238)
  Boys; Students; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Students in school. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1978 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1239)
  Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Boys; Photographic Prints; Students; Group Portraits; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Students in the school's playground. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1240)
  Boys; Students; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Children; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
- School's dining hall. 8.9 x 14 cm, 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1241)
  Drinks/Beverages; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Food; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints
- School's hall. 8.8 x 11.6 cm, 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1242)
  Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Architecture; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Photo of the school's dormitory. 13.4 x 8.4 cm, 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1243)
  Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints
- School's hall. 14 x 8.8 cm, 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1244)
  Furnishings; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints
- College de la Sainte Famille Church. 8.4 x 7.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1245)
  Religious Crosses; Architecture; Priests/Clergymen; Churches; Religious Imagery; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Exterior of the school. 8.4 x 7.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1246)
  Architecture; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints
- A portrait of a clergyman. 13.2 x 8.4 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1247)
  Individual Portraits; Men; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Facial Hair; Priests/Clergymen; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Group portrait of two men and a woman. 6.4 x 8.7 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1248)
  Men; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Women; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Students playing in the school's playground. 6 x 8.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1249)
  Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Boys; Students; Group Portraits; Children; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints
- A group portrait of several boys carrying walking sticks. 6.1 x 8.7 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1250)
  Boys; Hats; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Children; Canes/Walking Sticks; Gelatin Silver Prints
- A portrait. 10 x 6.2 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1251)
  Men; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Facial Hair; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Group portrait of boys with their teachers. 9.3 x 14.4 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1252)
  Teachers; Group Portraits; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Men; Children; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Priests/Clergymen; Hats; Water; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Group portrait. 8.8 x 13.5 cm, 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1253)
  Landscapes; Hats; Group Portraits; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Group portrait. 6.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1254)
  Boys; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Children; Priests/Clergymen; Hats; Bags/Purses; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair; Schools/Education; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Group portrait of two boys with a clergyman. 11.3 x 8.2 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1255)
  Helwan, Egypt; Priests/Clergymen; Boys; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Children; Men; Facial Hair
- Boys with a clergyman (Fr. A. Varotto) standing on top of a rock formation. 9.7 x 14.5 cm, 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1256)
  Teachers; Landscapes; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Children; Priests/Clergymen; Men; Facial Hair; Outdoors; Flags; Schools/Education; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Boys in front of the sea. 6.5 x 9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1257)
  Boys; Hats; Landscapes; Fishing; Photographic Prints; Seas; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Children; Group Portraits; Water; Facial Hair; Gelatin Silver Prints
- School photo. 8.8 x 12.5 cm, 1975 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1258)
  Boys; Students; Women; Men; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Teachers; Schools/Education; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Color Photography; Children; Priests/Clergymen
- The College de la Sainte Famille's orchestra. 8.8 x 12.7 cm, 1975 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1259)
  Schools/Education; Group Portraits; Musical Instruments; Teachers; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Students; Uniforms; Men; Color Photography; Boys; Children
- School photo. 8.8 x 12.7 cm, 1975 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1260)
  Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Uniforms; Students; Boys; Photographic Prints; Men; Helwan, Egypt; Facial Hair; Children; Color Photography; Facial Hair; Priests/Clergymen
- Students standing in line in school. 8.9 x 14 cm, 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1261)
  Schools/Education; Boys; Photographic Prints; Students; Uniforms; Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits; Crowds; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Students in school. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1262)
  Photographic Prints; Students; Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Hats; Teachers; Buildings; Men; Boys; Children; Facial Hair; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Group portrait of students in school. 8.9 x 14 cm, 1980 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1263)
  Schools/Education; Students; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Students in school. 8.9 x 14 cm, 1981 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1264)
  Boys; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Students; Helwan, Egypt; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints
- A crowd of boys. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, 1981 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1265)
  Photographic Prints; Students; Helwan, Egypt; Children; Boys; Crowds; Gelatin Silver Prints; Schools/Education; Group Portraits
- Students in the school's playground. 8.9 x 14 cm, 1981 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1266)
  Boys; Uniforms; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Students; Helwan, Egypt; Children; Group Portraits; Crowds; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Students in the school's playground. 8.9 x 14 cm, 1981 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1267)
  Schools/Education; Students; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Children; Group Portraits; Crowds; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Students in school. 8.9 x 14 cm, 1981 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1268)
  Photographic Prints; Students; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Uniforms; Children; Group Portraits; Crowds; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Students standing in line saluting the flag. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, 1981 (Object AD_MC_028_ref1269)